IHDA ANWARI

082262598163 | ihdaanwari5@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ihda-anwari | https://ihdas-playground.vercel.app/

Jln. Siliwangi Gang Bakri

I am a digital business student who has an interest in front-end developers, graphic designers, and UI/UX designers. I am capable of designing UI Websites with ReactJs and Laravel, I have experienced building websites as a full stack with laravel. I am also familiar with design tools like Adobe XD, Adobe Photoshop, Figma, Canva, and CorelDraw

Work Experiences

AVPN Asia - Singapore May 2022 - Aug 2022

Frontend Intern

- · Designed user interface (UI) and user experience (UX) for the website project using Figma design tool.
- Created mockup prototypes for the website project using ReactJs, incorporating previously designed UI/UX.
- Managed mockup data using the nocode Airtable application to ensure data reliability and consistency throughout the project development.

Univesitas Padjadjaran - Sumedang, Indonesia

Apr 2022 - Jun 2022

Teaching Assistant Web Development

- Teaching 2 classes that consists of >40 students to practice web development coding using HTML, CSS, PHP, and mySQL with Visual Studio Code and Sublime Text.
- · Arranging 2 classes schedule.
- · Creating >10 quizzes.

BEM Kema Unpad - Sumedang, Indonesia

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Project Lead

• Creating a website as a full-stack developer with Laravel that will be used by students that want to participate in a national competition called PKM a kind of business idea competition

Sekolah.mu - Jakarta Selatan, Indonesia

Sep 2022 - Dec 2022

Frontend Intern

- · Designed three website components for the front-end design system at Sekolah.mu.
- Implemented these components into Storybook to facilitate documentation and team collaboration.
- Created unit tests for each component to ensure quality and consistency in development.
- Achieved an average of 95% success rate in unit tests for each component, demonstrating design quality and accuracy
- · Actively participated in the development and improvement of features on the payment page.
- Collaborated with the development team to implement changes and ensure the successful launch of new features.
- Utilized Vue.js to create dynamic and responsive web components, thereby increasing the application's interactivity and usability.

Antares by Telkom - Bandung, Indonesia

Jan 2023 - Jun 2023

Developer Intern

- Developed 5 essential sub-menus to fulfill various application requirements, including tasks such as creating databases, establishing APIs, and designing front-end views.
- Proactively identified and resolved issues in over 10 sub-menus, resulting in improved functionality and an enhanced user experience.
- Utilized Vue is to create dynamic and responsive web components, thereby increasing the application's interactivity and usability.

Education Level

Padjadjaran University - Sumedang, Indonesia

Aug 2019 - Nov 2023 (Expected)

Bachelor Degree in Digital Business, 3.84/4.00

- · Received an A grade in UI/UX, Web Development, Web & Mobile Technology courses
- Received an A grade in Business Intelligence, Digital Marketing, and Social Media Management

Organisational Experience

Bem Kema Unpad - Sumedang, Indonesia

Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

Staff Academic and Inovation Department

- Manage and organize all social media posts including designing, publishing and draftingCreating website for PKM
- · Become the best staff in the second period

Hima Bisnis Digital - Sumedang, Indonesia

Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

• Manage and organize all social media posts including designing, publishing and drafting

Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Course (2022): Taking the Front-End Track at Generasi Gigih Program from Yayasan Anak Bangsa Bisa & GoTo
- **Tech Hard Skills**: Develop user interface website with ReactJs, Develop fullstack website with Laravel, Develop Mobile Interface with Flutter
- Business Hard Skills: Creating a dashboard with Tableau, creating associative analysis for recommendation with KNIME, familiar with social media tools analytics
- Design Hard Skills: Familiar with design tools like Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Coreldraw, Canva
- Language Skills: Bahasa Native
- Language Skills: English Proficient